Hi. Did Sheldon change the Wi-Fi password again?
Sheldon a encore changé le mot de passe du Wi-Fi ?
No spaces.
Sans espaces.
Okay. What makes you think you can get me to stop using your Wi-Fi?
Et tu crois pouvoir m'empêcher d'utiliser ton Wi-Fi ?
I believe that you're capable of great change.
Tu es capable de grands changements.
Like, when I finally got you to stop saying "Valentime's Day."
Comme quand je t'ai corrigé et que tu disais "Moël".
-Wanna hear something weird? -Sure.
- Il y a un truc bizarre. -Ah oui ?
In the year 2000...
En l'an 2000,
...Pope John Paul II was named an honorary Harlem Globetrotter.
le pape Jean-Paul II a été fait Harlem Globetrotter honoraire.
What are you talking about?
Quoi ?
You asked Penny if she wanted to hear something weird.
Tu parlais d'un truc bizarre.
Well, yeah, because I have something weird to tell her.
Oui, carje dois lui dire un truc bizarre.
-What's yours? -There's this guy, Jimmy Speckerman.
- Alors ? - Il y a un type, Jimmy Speckerman.
He used to torment me in high school.
Il me persécutait au lycée.
He sent me a message through Facebook.
Il m‘a contacté par Facebook.
-He's in town and wants to have drinks. -Okay, Penny.
Il veut qu‘on aille boire un verre.
If it were a game, here are your choices.
Si c'était un jeu, voilà tes options.
An e-mail from an old acquaintance...
Un e-mail d‘une Vieille connaissance,
...or the head of one of the largest religious institutions in the world...
ou le chef d‘une des plus grandes institutions religieuses
...slam-dunking to "Sweet Georgia Brown." Pick.
qui smashe sur du jazz. Choisis.
Just do it, because he's not gonna let it go.
Choisis, ou il va te harceler.
-Basketball Pope. -And that's how it's done.
- Le pape basketteur. - Et voilà.
What are you gonna do?
Que comptes-tu faire ?
-Are you gonna see him? -I don't know.
- Tu vas le voir ? - Aucune idée.
Is this the fellow who peed in your Hawaiian Punch?
C‘est le type qui a pissé dans ta boisson ?
No, that was a different guy.
Non, un autre.
Was he the one who wedgied you so hard your testicle reascended...
Celui qui t‘a tiré le slip si fort qu'il t‘a remonté les couilles,
...and you spent your whole Christmas break waiting for it to come back down?
et que tu as passé les vacances a attendre qu'elle redescendent ?
No, that was a different different guy.
Non, un autre.
Was he the one who used your head to open a nut?
Celui qui a cassé une noix avec ta tête ?
Was he the one who made you eat your arm hair?
Celui qui t‘a fait manger tes poils de bras ?
No, but actually, that was this guy's sister.
Non, c'était la sœur de ce type.
-Well, what do you think he wants? -I don't know.
- Que veut-il ? - Aucune idée.
The holidays are just around the corner.
C‘est presque Noël.
Maybe he wants to see if he can lodge the other testicle up there.
Il veut peut-être te remonter les boules.
I told you. That was a different guy.
C‘était un autre type.
Mm, that's too bad. Could've spent New Year's Eve waiting for the ball to drop.
Sinon, t'aurais pu les remplacer par les boules du sapin.
It's 2 am. What are you doing up?
Il est 2 h du matin. Tu fais quoi ?
Nobel Prize acceptance ceremony streaming live from Stockholm.
Cérémonie de remise du prix Nobel en direct de Stockholm.
Sure. Wanna see what all the scientists are wearing this year.
Pour voir la mode chez les scientifiques cette année.
Look at these men.
Regarde ces types.
They've managed to win the top science prize in the world...
Ils ont remporté le meilleur prix de science
...with no more understanding of the quantum underpinnings...
sans comprendre plus les fondements quantiques
...of the expansion of the early universe than God gave a goose.
de l‘expansion de l‘univers qu‘une oie.
You should pay attention, Leonard. Someday it's gonna be you up there.
Ecoute bien, Leonard. Un jour tu seras a leur place.
-Thanks. -So, what's got you up?
- Merci. - Pourquoi t'es debout ?
Did you have a bad clam?
T'as mangé une mauvaise huître ?
-I didn't have clams. -I don't watch you 24 hours a day.
- J'en ai pas mangé. - Je ne te flique pas.
I don't know what you do.
Je ne sais pas ce que tu fais.
It's this Jimmy Speckerman thing. I can't decide ifl should agree...
Jimmy Speckerman. J'ignore si je dois
...to see him or not. That might be because the last time I ran into him...
le voir ou pas. La dernière fois que je l'ai vu,
...he made me floss with my own shoelaces.
il m‘a fait utiliser mes lacets comme fil dentaire.
Wear loafers.
Mets des mocassins.
Look at Dr. Saul Perlmutter up there clutching that Nobel Prize.
Ce Dr Saul Perlmutter qui s‘agrippe au prix Nobel.
What's the matter, Saul? Afraid someone's gonna steal it.
Qu'y a-t-il, Saul ? T'as peur qu'on te le voie.
Like you stole Einstein's cosmological constant?
Comme t‘a volé la constante d'Einstein ?
You know what? lam tired of living in fear of this guy.
J'en ai marre d‘avoir peur de lui.
I'm gonna go see him...
Je vais le voir
...and say the things I should have said in high school.
et lui dire ce que j'aurais dû lui dire au lycée.
"Pick on someone your own size."
"Ne t'attaque pas aux plus faibles."
"No, you did not have sex with my mother."
”Non, tu n'as pas couché avec ma mère."
And, "Yes, I do know why I'm hitting myself."
Et : "Oui, je sais pourquoi je me frappe."
Oh. Now Perlmutter shaking the king's hand.
Perlmutter sert la main du roi.
Yeah. Check for your watch, Gustaf, he might've lifted it.
Gustaf, vérifie qu'il t'ait pas piqué ta montre.
I love this dress.
J‘adore cette robe.
-How come I never see you wear it? -Because when I wear it, it's a shirt.
- Tu ne la mets jamais. - Sur moi, c‘est une chemise.
So, what's Howard doing tonight?
Que fait Howard ce soir ?
Oh, they all went with Leonard to confront his childhood bully.
Ils sont allés voir le type qui brutalisait Leonard.
When Leonard gets back, I'd love to check serotonin levels.
Au retour de Leonard, je vérifierai sa sérotonine.
Do you think he'd let me draw a syringe full of his blood?
Il voudra queje lui fasse une prise de sang ?
Hmm. He's not crazy about needles.
Il n'aime pas les aiguilles.
But if you get him to go jogging, it'll just pour out of his nose.
Mais fais-Ie courir, il saignera du nez.
I don't think I can meet the girl who was always mean to me.
Je ne pourrais pas rencontrer la fille que me brutalisait.
Tammy Bodnick. One time while I was in gym class...
Tammy Bodnick. Une fois, en cours de gym,
...she stole all my clothes and left an elf costume in my locker.
elle m‘a piqué mes fringues et a laissé un costume d‘elfe.
-Oh, that's awful. -Worst part was it was too big.
- C‘est affreux. - Il était trop grand.
That's nothing. In ninth grade, the girls put Rogaine in my hand lotion.
En 3e, on a mis du Minoxidil dans ma crème.
Within six months, the nicknames began to fly.
En six mois, j'ai eu un max de surnoms.
I think the one that hurt the most was Gorilla Fingers Fowler.
Le pire, c‘était la Petite gorille.
What about you?
Et toi ?
Oh, I don't know. My school was a nice place. We didn't have bullies.
Mon lycée était bien. Il n‘y avait pas de brutes.
Come on, no one ever gave anyone mean nicknames, or picked on them...
Personne ne t‘ajamais donné de surnoms méchants,
...or put gum in their hairy knuckles so the nurse had get it out?
ou mis du chewing-gum dans tes cheveux ?
No, we weren't really like that.
On n‘était pas comme ça.
We played pranks on each other, but it was never mean.
On se faisait des blagues, mais pas méchantes.
This girl, Kathy Geiger, got good grades so we blindfolded her...
Kathy Geiger avait de bonnes notes, on lui a bandé les yeux,
...tied her up and left her in a cornfield overnight.
on l‘a attachée et laissée une nuit dans un champ.
-God. That's awful. -No, it was funny. Everyone laughed.
- C‘est affreux. - C‘était drôle. Tout le monde a ri.
Did Kathy Geiger laugh?
Kathy Geiger aussi ?
Uh, probably. It's hard to say. She kind of had an ear of corn in her mouth.
Dur à dire, elle avait un épi de mais dans la bouche.
Who would've thought.
Qui l'eut cru.
Fuzzy Fingers Fowler is best friends with a bully.
Petite gorille est amie avec une brute.
-What--? I was not a bully. -Kind of sounds like you were.
- Je n‘étais pas une brute. - On dirait que si.
And maybe a felon.
Et peut-être même une criminelle.
Shh. That's how you wind up in a cornfield.
C‘est comme ça qu'on se retrouve dans un champ.
Is that him over there?
C‘est lui là:—bas ?
How about that guy? He looks like he'd hate you.
Et ce type ? Il pourrait te détester.
-I can really do this by myself. -We're here to support you.
- Je peux le faire seul. - On veut te soutenir.
No, you're not. You're here to see ifl get my underwear pulled over my head.
Non. Vous voulez le voir me remonter le slip.
You wore underwear? Ha, ha. You fool.
T'as mis un slip ? Idiot.
-You figured out what you're gonna say? -You bet.
- Tu sais quoi lui dire ? - Tu m'étonnes.
lam going to make him apologize for all the crap he pulled on me in school.
Je vais le faire s'excuser pour tout ce qu'il m‘a fait au lycée.
That's quite a list. I can't read your handwriting.
Sacrée liste. J'arrive pas ate lire.
What's that word?
C‘est quoi ?
Scrotum.
Scrotum.
What's that one?
Etça?
Uh, stapled.
Ag rafé.
Leonard?
Leonard ?
Yeah, you too.
Oui, moi aussi.
Uh, Jimmy, this is Sheldon, and Raj, and Howard.
Jimmy, voici Sheldon, Raj et Howard.
-Hi. -Fellows. Can I get a beer?
Messieurs. Une bière.
Wow, look at you. Little Leonard Hofstadter.
Regarde-toi. Le petit Leonard Hofstadter.
I hear you're a big-time scientist now.
T'es un scientifique réputé.
And there's the first zinger. Ouch.
La première pique.
-l'm doing okay, I guess. JIMMY: Okay?
- Je me débrouille. - Quoi ?
Come on, I read online you're a physicist at a university. You won some medal.
J'ai lu que t‘étais physicien. T'as gagné une médaille.
-The Newcomb medal. -Yeah. Congratulations.
- La médaille Newcomb. - Oui. Félicitations.
Congratulations? For the Newcomb med--?
Félicitations ? Pour la médaille…
Oh, please. That's the scientific equivalent...
C‘est l'équivalent scientifique
...of a smiley-face sticker on your homework.
d'un bon point a l'école.
-It sounded like a big deal. -Oh, good Lord.
- Ça semblait important. - Seigneur.
Are we gonna stand here and listen to him tear Leonard apart like this?
On va rester la et le laisser descendre Leonard ?
-Hey, I won a Newcomb medal too. -My point.
- J'ai aussi eu cette médaille. - Justement.
You should've seen this guy back in the day. Huh?
Vous auriez dû le voir a l‘époque.
He was so little, he could fit anywhere.
Il était rikiki, il passait partout.
Lockers, trash cans.
Casiers, poubelles.
Oh, man, how did you get inside that backpack?
Comment t'es rentré dans ce sac a dos ?
Oh, I can't take all the credit. You helped a lot.
Le mérite t'en revient aussi. Tu m'as aidé.
-We were practically a comedy team. -Like the Black Death in Europe.
- On était presque un duo comique. - Comme la Peste noire et l‘Europe.
Jimmy, I'm kind of curious why you wanted to see me.
Jimmy, pourquoi voulais-tu me voir ?
Okay, here it is. l have this great money-making idea.
J'ai une super idée pour gagner du fric.
I need a gear-head to get it to the finish line.
Il me faut un expert en moteurs.
Mm, technically, Howard's the gear-head. Leonard's just a dime-store laser jockey.
L‘expert, c‘est Howard. Leonard est expert en stéréo.
What's the idea?
C‘est quoi ton idée ?
-This is just between us, right? -Right.
- Ca reste entre nous. - Oui.
That sounds amazing. First movie I'm watching, Annie.
Ça a l‘air super. Le premier que je materai, Annie.
How exactly would these glasses work?
Comment elles fonctionneraient ?
How the hell should I know? That's whyl need a nerd.
J'en sais rien. C‘est pour ça qu'il me faut un nerd.
I don't think something like that's even possible.
Je ne pense pas que ce soit possible.
Aw, come on. You could figure it out. You're, like, the smartest guy.
Tu pourrais le faire. T'es le plus intelligent.
The smartest--? All right.
Le plus...
I may not have a firm grasp on sarcasm, but, uh, even I know that was a doozy.
Je ne suis pas calé en sarcasmes, mais même moi,j'ai compris.
You can't live in fear of this man forever.
Tu ne dois plus avoir peur de lui.
-Sheldon, I got this. -You clearly don't.
- Sheldon, c‘est bon. - Pas du tout.
What my spineless friend lacks the courage to say...
Ce que mon ami lâche essaie de dire,
...is you're a terrible person who took advantage of his tiny size...
c‘est que vous avez profité de sa petite taille,
...his uncoordinated nature, and his congenital lack of masculinity.
de son manque de coordination et de son manque de masculinité.
-Sheldon. -Leonard, l platonically love you, man.
- Sheldon. - Je t'aime platoniquement.
But face it, you're a mess.
Mais c‘est la Vérité.
I don't understand.
Je ne saisis pas.
I think what he's trying to say is that maybe...
Il essaie de dire
...in high school, you picked on me a little bit.
qu'au lycée, tu me brutalisais un peu.
A little bit? The man super-glued Hershey's kisses to your nipples.
Un peu ? Il t‘a collé des chocolats sur les mamelons.
That's funny because those aren't the kind of kisses you want on your nipples.
J'aime bien le chocolat en général, mais pas la.
-What is that? -This is a list...
- C‘est quoi ? - Une liste
...of your heinous acts against Leonard...
de vos actes odieux envers Leonard,
...one of which is certainly the cause of him wetting his bed well into his teens.
dont un qui l‘a fait mouiller son lit jusqu‘à l'adolescence.
Fourteen is not-- Uh, yeah, never mind.
14 ans, ce n‘est pas... Laisse tomber.
What's this word?
C‘est écrit quoi la ?
Nancy.
Nancy.
You called me Nancy for three years.
Tu m'as appelé Nancy pendant trois ans.
You really need to work on your penmanship.
Tu devrais écrire mieux.
I don't know what to say.
Je ne sais pas quoi dire.
I thought we were just having some fun.
Je croyais qu'on s'amusait.
Well, it wasn't fun for me.
Pas moi.
You're being too kind, Leonard. You ruined him.
Tu es trop gentil, Leonard. Vous l'avez détruit.
Come on, guys.
Allez, venez.
-That was pretty bad-ass, dude. -I help the weak.
- Un vrai dur. - J'aide les faibles.
It's yet another way I'm exactly like Batman.
Je suis vraiment comme Batman.
And for the record, Jimmy wasn't the reason I wet the bed.
Etje n'ai pas mouillé mon lit a cause de Jimmy.
That one has my mother written all over it.
C‘est plutôt ma mère.
Anyway, I'm really sorry I made fun of your stutter in high school.
Désolée de m'être moquée de ton bégaiement.
You're doing great.
Tu t'en sors bien.
Ah. Okay, well, I'm sorry you feel that way.
Désolée que tu penses ça.
-No one wants to hear my apologies. -Your mistake is doing it over the phone.
- Elles refusent mes excuses. - Tu le fais par téléphone.
I mean, if they could look into your eyes, they'd melt.
De visu, c‘est mieux.
It doesn't matter what you did in the past. You're a good person.
Qu'importe ton passé. Tu es quelqu'un de bien.
Yeah, that's easy for you to say. You weren'tjust called a "b-b-bitch."
Facile à dire pour toi. On ne t‘a pas traitée de pétasse.
Perhaps you could assuage your guilt through altruism.
Apaise ta culpabilité par l'altruisme.
Which word's tripping you up?
T'as pas compris quoi ?
Assuage or altruism?
Apaise ou altruisme ?
Both.
Les deux.
You'll feel better by doing something nice for someone.
Tu te sentiras mieux en faisant le bien.
-Oh, I actually knew that. -I never doubted you.
- Je le savais. - Je m'en doutais.
Every other week, I serve at a soup kitchen downtown.
Je sers àla soupe populaire.
-Ah. What else can I do? -There's Habitat for Humanity.
- Quoi d‘autre ? - Habitat pour l‘humanité.
Building houses for the poor.
Des maisons pour les pauvres.
I don't have my own house, I'm gonna build one for someone else?
Je n'ai pas de maison, alors en construire pour d'autres ?
How about donating some of your clothes?
Donner certains de tes Vêtements ?
Oh, my God, that's perfect, because I have so many clothes I don't wear.
Parfait, j'ai plein de fringues queje ne mets plus.
They're taking up space I go shopping to buy more.
J'en profiterai pour en acheter d‘autres.
l have no place to put it. This would fix that.
Etje manque de place. Parfait.
-What about helping people? -And helping people.
- Et aider les gens ? - Et aider les gens.
-Here's your cocoa. -Oh.
Ton chocolat chaud.
-Half and half instead of whole milk? -Yes.
- Demi-écrémé ? - Oui.
-Heated to precisely 183 degrees?
Chauffé a 83 degrés ?
Seven little marshmallows, no more, no less?
Sept petits guimauves en tout ?
You got one for good luck.
Plus une pour te porter chance.
I'll get it.
J‘y vais.
One for good luck.
Une pour dela chance.
Must be the kind of math they do at Princeton.
Le genre de maths qu‘ils font à Princeton.
I wanna apologize for stapling your balls...
Désolé de t‘avoir agrafé les couilles...
...throwing you naked into the girls' locker room...
de t‘avoirjeté nu dans les vestiaires des filles,
...stuffing that parrot down your pants.
d‘avoir mis ce perroquet dans ton caleçon.
What's this word?
C‘est écrit quoi ?
-Laxative. -Oh.
Laxatif.
Right. Junior prom. Ha, ha.
Oui. Au bal de promo.
That was not cool, man.
Ce n‘était pas cool.
I am so, so sorry.
Je suis navré.
-Really? -Yeah.
Vraiment ?
ljust hope you can forgive me.
J'espère que tu me pardonneras.
-You're a beautiful guy. -Oh, well, yeah. Thanks, Jimmy.
- Tu es quelqu'un de bon. -Oui. Merci,Jimmy.
-Are you okay to drive? -Yeah, yeah.
Tu peux conduire ?
I drive better drunk, you know?
Je conduis mieux bourré.
It makes you pay attention.
Je fais plus attention.
No. Come on in. I'll make you a cup of coffee.
Non. Entré. Je te fais un café.
-I wouldn't be imposing? -No.
- Je ne veux pas m'imposer. - Non.
Yes.
Si.
-Sheldon, we can't let him drive. -Then take away his keys...
- Sheldon, il ne peut pas conduire. - Prends—lui ses clés
...and make him wander the streets with the other drunks.
et laisse-Ie errer dans la rue comme un ivrogne.
You remember Sheldon, and Raj, and Howard.
Tu te souviens de Sheldon, Raj et Howard.
Not really, no.
Non, pas vraiment.
It's funny, huh? Back in school, I was the winner, and you were the loser.
Au lycée, j‘étais un gagnant, et toi un perdant.
And now we're reversed.
Maintenant, c‘est l'inverse.
You're the winner.
C‘est toi le gagnant.
You'd think a winner could make a decent cup of cocoa.
Un gagnant devrait pouvoir faire un bon chocolat chaud.
-Mind ifl use your bathroom? -Yeah. It's just back there.
- Où sont tes toilettes ? - Juste derrière.
How about that? After all these years...
Après toutes ces années,
...your big, bad high-school bully finally apologizes.
ton grand bourreau s'excuse enfin.
-You know what would be nice? -What's that?
- Vous savez ce qui serait bien ? - Quoi ?
As a symbolic gesture to all the bullies who've tormented us for years...
Comme un geste symbolique envers toutes les brutes,
...we open our home to Jimmy, and once he's asleep, we kill him.
ouvrons notre maison a Jimmy, et quand il dort, on le tue.
I said it would be nice. I didn't say we should do it.
J'ai dit que ce serait bien. Pas qu'on devrait le faire.
Oh. I feel just like Mother Teresa.
Je suis comme mére Teresa.
Except for the virgin part. That ship sailed a long time ago.
Sauf que je ne suis plus vierge depuis un bail.
I think Mother Teresa would've washed the clothes first.
Mère Teresa aurait lavé ses fringues avant.
Yeah, well, I bet her laundry room wasn't down five flights of stairs.
Sa buanderie n‘était pas cinq étages plus bas.
You know, giving really is better than receiving.
Donner, c‘est mieux que recevoir.
Oh. I used to think it was such a cliché, but it seems to be the--
Je trouvais ça cliché, mais ça semble être…
Ah! Look at these cute jeans someone just threw away.
Ce jeans est chouette, quelqu'un l'ajeté.
Donated.
Donné.
Yes, to a poor waitress who loves a boot-cut.
Oui, à une pauvre serveuse qui aime les coupes larges.
-Penny. -Come on. They would be so cute on me.
- Penny. - Il m‘irait super bien.
Ah! They'd go great with this sweater.
Super bien avec ce pull.
I don't think Mother Teresa would-- Oh, that is adorable.
Mère Teresa n‘aurait... C‘est adorable.
-Leonard? -Yeah?
Leonard ?
In case it comes up again, this right here is an imposition.
Au cas où, sache qu'il s‘impose.
What was I supposed to do? He needed a place to sleep.
Il n‘avait nulle part où récupérer.
You're soft. This world's gonna chew you up and spit you out.
Tu es trop tendre. Ce monde va t'avaler et te recracher.
When did I have tacos?
J'ai mangé des tacos quand ?
Morning,Jimmy.
Bonjour, Jimmy.
Oh, there it is. Tacos.
Voilà les tacos.
-Man, I tied one on. -Yeah, you did.
- Sacré rot. - Oui.
So, uh, listen, it was great to see you again.
Ecoute, c‘était super de te revoir.
And thanks for the apology.
Merci pour les excuses.
What apology?
Quelles excuses ?
For all the crappy stuff you did to me in high school.
Pour toutes les crasses faites au lycée.
Oh, jeez, you're still harping on that? What a puss.
Mince, t'es encore là:—dessus ? Quelle mauviette.
-That's my French toast. -lt's good.
- C‘est mon pain perdu. - C‘est bon.
You really know your way around a kitchen, Nancy.
T'es doué en cuisine, Nancy.
I'm not going to say I told you so, but we could've killed him.
Au risque de me répéter, on aurait pu le tuer.
I might kill him right now.
Je peux le tuer maintenant.
The Dark Knight has your back.
Le Chevalier noir est avec toi.
He's scared, but he has your back.
Il a peur, mais il est la.
Hey, Jimmy, it's time for you to go.
Tu vas devoir partir.
-Yeah, let me just finish this. -No. You're done.
- Laisse—moi finir ça. - Non, t'as fini.
-I want you out of my apartment now. -Well said, Boy Wonder.
- Sors de chez moi. - Bravo, Robin.
Or what?
Sinon quoi ?
Don't answer. That's a trick question. I speak from experience.
Ne réponds pas. C‘est un piège. Je m‘y connais.
I'm not afraid of you anymore, Jimmy.
Je n'ai plus peur de toi, Jimmy.
Now, get out.
Allez, sors d'ici.
You did it. You stood up to your bully.
T'as tenu tête a ta brute.
Yeah, I feel pretty good about myself.
Je me sens super bien.
Do you think we can outrun him?
Tu crois qu'on court plus vite que lui ?
I don't need to outrun him. ljust need to outrun you.
Qu‘importe, je cours plus vite que toi.
I don't feel good about this.
Je ne le sens pas.
Well, then, sit in the car and keep it running.
Va dans la voiture et attends—nous.
You were right. A whole new load.
T‘avais raison. De nouvelles fringues.
Come on, yoga top. Momma needs a new yoga top.
Un top pour le yoga. Il m'en faut un.
Check it out, Bernadette. Suede boots. Your size.
Regarde, Bernadette. Des bottes en daim. A ta taille.
God, they're cute. Oh, why did they have to be cute?
Elles pouvaient pas être moches ?
Wait, wait, wait, guys. Just hang on.
Attendez voir.
What is it? The fuzz?
Quoi ? Les keufs ?
Oh, look at us. What are we doing?
Regardez—nous. On fait quoi ?
l was following you to a life of crime...
Je te suivais dans tes actes criminels
...looking forward to the day we might be cell mates.
en attendant qu'on partage une cellule.
I don't know about Bernadette.
Pour Bernadette, je sais pas.
No, this is wrong.
Non, c‘est mal.
Let's put everything back. Come on.
Reposons tout. Allez.
Here.
Tiens.
It's okay, I serve soup to poor people.
C‘est pas grave, je bosse àla soupe populaire.
[English - us - an]
[French]